const questionBank = [{
    question: "What club was Todd Howard famously in?",
    answers: ["Chess", "Newspaper", "Tiny Instrument Ensemble", "Drama"],
    correctAnswer: "Chess",
},
{
    question: "What game did Todd Howard NOT have a part in?",
    answers: ["Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim", "The Terminator: Future Shock", "Fallout 76", "Fallout New Vegas"],
    correctAnswer: "Fallout 76",
},
{
    question: "What year was Nintendo founded?",
    answers: ["1889", "1977", "1973", "1985"],
    correctAnswer: "1889",
},
{
    question: "Who was the Prime Minister of Greece during World War I?",
    answers: ["Constantine I", "Eleftherios Venizelos", "Ioannis Metaxas", "Kyriakos Mitsotakis"],
    correctAnswer: "Eleftherios Venizelos",
},
{
    question: "Who is the only person to win Nobel Prizes in two separate sciences?",
    answers: ["Marie Curie", "Albert Einstein", "Neil DeGrasse Tyson", "Niels Bohr"],
    correctAnswer: "Marie Curie",
},
{
    question: "What is located at geographic coordinates (0, 0)?",
    answers: ["A buoy", "An island", "Nothing", "A rock with a couple of seagulls on it"],
    correctAnswer: "A buoy",
},
{
    question: "What company was Steve Jobs NOT involved with?",
    answers: ["Pixar", "Atari", "Apple", "IBM"],
    correctAnswer: "IBM",
},
{
    question: "What territory must the UK lose for the sun to set on the British Empire?",
    answers: ["The Cayman Islands", "The Pitcairn Islands", "Montserrat", "Turks and Caicos Islands"],
    correctAnswer: "The Pitcairn Islands",
},
{
    question: "Where did the Polynesians never migrate to?",
    answers: ["The Philippines", "New Guinea", "New Zealand", "Tasmania"],
    correctAnswer: "Tasmania",
},
{
    question: "What is the oldest known work of animation in Japan?",
    answers: ["Imokawa Mukuzo Genkanban no Maki", "Katsudō Shashin", "Namakura Gatana", "Hakujaden"],
    correctAnswer: "Katsudō Shashin",
},
{
    question: "What is the highest-grossing franchise in the world?",
    answers: ["Pokémon", "Hello Kitty", "Mickey Mouse", "Winnie the Pooh"],
    correctAnswer: "Pokémon",
},
{
    question: "What country is LEGO based out of?",
    answers: ["United States", "Switzerland", "China", "Denmark"],
    correctAnswer: "Denmark",
},
{
    question: "How many boxes of Kraft Dinner does Canada purchase per week?",
    answers: ["1 million", "1.7 million", "2.2 million", "3.5 million"],
    correctAnswer: "1.7 million",
},
{
    question: "What actor put a life-size statue of themselves in the window of their house?",
    answers: ["David Hasslehoff", "Nick Cage", "Emma Watson", "Willem Dafoe"],
    correctAnswer: "David Hasslehoff",
},
{
    question: "What was once an Olympic Event?",
    answers: ["Sculpting", "Cooking", "Treasure Hunting", "Jousting"],
    correctAnswer: "Sculpting",
},
{
    question: "In The Wizard of Oz, what is Dorothy’s last name?",
    answers: ["Baum", "Gale", "Parker", "Sayers"],
    correctAnswer: "Gale",
},
{
    question: "Where is the International Bowling Museum and Hall of Fame located?",
    answers: ["St. Louis, Missouri", "Henderson, Nevada", "Tulsa, Oklahoma", "Arlington, Texas"],
    correctAnswer: "Arlington, Texas",
},
{
    question: "Which Dr. Seuss book began as a bet?",
    answers: ["Horton Hears A Who", "Green Eggs and Ham", "Fox in Socks", "Wacky Wednesday"],
    correctAnswer: "Green Eggs and Ham",
},
{
    question: "Which voice actor is accredited with the most roles?",
    answers: ["Yuri Lowenthal", "Bryce Papenbrook", "Mel Blanc", "Cherami Leigh"],
    correctAnswer: "Mel Blanc",
},
{
    question: "What console was the first with a “Directional Pad”?",
    answers: ["NES", "Game & Watch", "Intellivision", "Entex “Select a Game”"],
    correctAnswer: "Entex “Select a Game”",
},
];

export { questionBank }